A Guide to the Minutes of the Virginia Board of Nursing, 1975-2020.
Library of Virginia
- Minutes of the Virginia Board of Nursing, 1975-2020.
  - Accession 52644 (2003-2005, 2008)., Extent: 3 cu. ft. (3 boxes)
    - Boards/Committees (folder 2 of 2), 2008 July. (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Boards/Committees, 2008 Aug. (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Boards/Committees (folder 1 of 2), 2008 Sept. (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Boards/Committees (folder 2 of 2), 2008 Sept. (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Boards/Committees, 2008 Oct. (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Committee of the Joint Boards of Nursing and Medicine, 2008 Oct 15. (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Boards/Committees, 2008 Nov. (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Full Board (folder 1 of 2), 2008 Nov 17-20. (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Full Board (folder 2 of 2), 2008 Nov 17-20. (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Boards/Committees, 2008 Dec. (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Committee of the Joint Board of Nursing and Medicine, 2008 Dec 3. (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Accession 52676 (2009)., Extent: .7 cu. ft. (2 boxes)
    Minutes, 2009, for the Full Board (which may also include education committee, formal hearing, informal conference, special conference, telephone conference minutes held during board week), Committee of the Joint Boards of Nursing and Medicine, Education Special Conference Committee, Formal Hearings, Informal Conference Committees, Special Conference Committees, and Telephone Conference calls. Includes final, approved minutes without signatures, as well as some draft, unapproved minutes. Full board minutes may also include attachments, including revenue and expenditure summaries, correspondence, legislation, presentations, regulations, and reports.
    - Informal Conference, 2009 Jan 8, 14, 15. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Full Board, 2009 Jan. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Medication Aide Curriculum Task Force, 2009. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Committee for the Joint Boards of Nursing and Medicine, 2009 Feb 18. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Informal Conferences, 2009 Feb. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Medication Aide Curriculum Review Committee, 2009 Feb. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Special Conferences, 2009 Feb. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Telephone Conference Call, 2009 Feb 10. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Full Board, 2009 Mar 16-19. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Informal Conferences, 2009 Mar. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Committee for the Joint Boards of Nursing and Medicine, 2009 Apr 15. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Formal Hearings, 2009 Apr. (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Informal Conferences, 2009 Apr. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Special Conference Committees, 2009 Apr. (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Telephone Conference Call, 2009 Apr 10. (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Full Board, 2009 May 18-21. (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Informal Conferences, 2009 May. (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Informal Conferences, 2009 June. (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Special Conference Committees, 2009 June. (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Telephone Conference Call, 2009 June 16. (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Education Special Conference Committee, 2009 July 15. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Full Board, 2009 July 20-23. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Informal Conferences, 2009 July. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Telephone Conference Calls, 2009 July. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Formal hearings, 2009 Aug. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Informal Conferences, 2009 Aug. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Special Conference Committees, 2009 Aug. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Telephone Conference Call, 2009 Aug. (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Education Informal Conference Committee, 2009 Sept. (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Full Board, 2009 Sept 14-17. (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Informal Conferences, 2009 Sept. (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Formal Hearings, 2009 Oct. (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Informal Conferences, 2009 Oct. (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Special Conference Committees, 2009 Oct. (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Telephone Conference Call, 2009 Oct. (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Education Informal Conference Committee, 2009 Nov. (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Full Board, 2009 Nov 16-19. (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Informal Conferences, 2009 Nov. (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Massage Therapy Advisory Board, 2009 Nov. (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Committee for the Joint Boards of Nursing and Medicine, 2009 Dec. (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Formal Hearings, 2009 Dec. (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Informal Conferences, 2009 Dec. (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Special Conference Committe, 2009 Dec. (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Accession 53924 (2016-2020)., Extent: 3.85 cu. ft. (11 boxes)
    Board meeting packets, 2016-2020. Includes full board minutes, agency subordinate informal conference minutes and special conference committee minutes. Also includes minutes for the Bylaws Committee, Committee of the Joint Boards of Nursing and Medicince, Education Informal Conference Committee, Massage Therapy Advisory Board, Nurse Aide Curriculum Stakeholders Committee, and the PICC Line Insertion and Removal Committee.
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2016 Jan. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Full Board, 2016 Jan 27. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2016 Feb. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Special Conference Committees, 2016 Feb. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Telephone Conference Call, 2016 Feb 4. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2016 Mar. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Full Board, 2016 Mar 21-24. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2016 Apr. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Committee of the Joint Boards of Nursing and Medicine, 2016 Apr 15. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Massage Therapy Advisory Board, 2016 Apr 6. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Special Conference Committees, 2016 Apr. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2016 May. (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Full Board, 2016 May 16-19. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2016 June. (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Committee of the Joint Boards of Nursing and Medicine, 2016 June 8. (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Special Conference Committees, 2016 June. (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Telephone Conference Call, 2016 June 7. (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2016 July. (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Education Informal Conference Committee, 2016 July 13. (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Full Board, 2016 July 16-18. (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Nurse Aide Curriculum Stakeholders, 2016 July 14. (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2016 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Special Conference Committees, 2016 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2016 Sept. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Education Committee, 2016 Sept 13. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Full Board, 2016 Spt 19-22. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2016 Oct. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Committee of the Joint Boards of Nursing and Medicine, 2016 Oct 12. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Special Conference Committees, 2016 Oct. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2016 Nov. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Education Committee, 2016 Nov 9. (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Full Board, 2016 Nov 14-17. (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2016 Dec. (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Committee of the Joint Boards of Nursing and Medicine, 2016 Dec 7. (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Massage Therapy Advisory Board, 2016 Dec 1. (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Special Conference Committees, 2016 Dec. (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Telephone Conference Call, 2016 Dec 7. (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2017 Jan. (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Education Committee, 2017 Jan 11. (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Full Board, 2017 Jan 23-26. (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2017 Feb. (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Committee of the Joint Boards of Nursing and Medicine, 2017 Feb 8. (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Special Conference Committees, 2017 Feb. (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Telephone Conference Call, 2017 Feb 28. (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2017 Mar. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Full Board, 2017 Mar 20-23. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Telephone Conference Call, 2017 Mar 16. (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2017 Apr. (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Committee of the Joint Boards of Nursing and Medicine, 2017 Apr 12. (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Special Conference Committees, 2017 Apr. (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Telephone Conference Call, 2017 Apr 12. (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2017 May. (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Education Committee, 2017 May 10. (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - full Board, 2017 May 15-17. (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2017 June. (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Committee of the Joint Boards of Nursing and Medicine, 2017 June 7. (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Special Conference Committees, 2017 June. (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Telephone Conference Call, 2017 June 15. (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2017 July. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - By-laws Committee - Guidance Document, 2017 July 18. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Education Committee, 2017 July 12. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Full Board, 2017 July 17-20. (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Nurse Aide Education Curriculum Committee, 2017 July 18. (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - PICC Line Insertion and Removal Committee - Guidance Document, 2017 July 18. (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2017 Aug. (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Education Committee, 2017 Aug 13. (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Special Conference Committees, 2017 Aug. (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2017 Sept. (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Education Committee, 2017 Sept 13. (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Full Board, 2017 Sept 18-20. (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Nurse Aide Curriculum Committee, 2017 Sept 21. (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2017 Oct. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Committee for the Joint Boards of Nursing and Medicine, 2017 Oct 11. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Special Conference Committees, 2017 Oct. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Telephone Conference Call, 2017 Oct 3. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2017 Nov. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Education Committee, 2017 Nov 8. (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Full Board, 2017 Nov 13-17. (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Massage Therapy Advisory Board, 2017 Nov 7. (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Telephone Conference Call, 2017 Nov 16. (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2017 Dec 11. (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Committee of the Joint Boards of Nursing and Medicine, 2017 Dec 6. (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Special Conference Committees, 2017 Dec. (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2018 Jan. (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Education Committee, 2018 Jan 17. (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Full Board, 2018 Jan 29-31. (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Telephone Conference Call, 2018 Jan 17. (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2018 Feb. (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Committee of the Joint Boards of Nursing and Medicine, 2018 Feb 17. (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Special Conference Committees, 2018 Feb. (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2018 Mar. (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Education Committee, 2018 Mar 14. (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Full Board, 2018 Mar 26-29. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2018 Apr. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Committee of the Joint Boards of Nursing and Medicine, 2018 Apr 11. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Special Conference Committees, 2018 Apr. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2018 May. (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Education Committee, 2018 May 2. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Full Board, 2018 May 14-17. (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2018 June. (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Special Conference Committees, 2018 June. (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2018 July. (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Education Committee, 2018 July 10. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Full Board, 2018 July 16-18. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2018 Aug. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Special Conference Committees, 2018 Aug. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2018 Sept. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Education Committee, 2018 Sept 5. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Full Board, 2018 Sept 17-20. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2018 Oct. (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Committee of the Joint Boards of Nursing and Medicine, 2018 Oct 11. (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Special Conference Committees, 2018 Oct. (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Telephone Conference Call, 2018 Oct 23. (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2018 Nov. (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Education Committee, 2018 Nov 1. (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Full Board, 2018 Nov 13-15. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Massage Therapy Advisory Board, 2018 Nov 5. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Special Conference Committees, 2018 Nov. (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2018 Dec. (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Special Conference Committees, 2018 Dec. (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Telephone Conference Call, 2018 Dec 19. (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2019 Jan. (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Full Board, 2019 Jan 28-31. (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2019 Feb. (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Committee of the Joint Boards of Nursing and Medicine, 2019 Feb 13. (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Special Conference Committees, 2019. (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Telephone Conference Call, 2019 Feb 20. (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Telephone Conference Call, 2019 feb 28. (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2019 Mar. (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Education Committee, 2019 Mar 6. (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Full Board, 2019 Mar 18-21. (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2019 Apr. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Committee of the Joint Boards of Nursing and Medicine, 2019 Apr 10. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Special Conference Committees, 2019 Apr. (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Telephone Conference Calls, 2019 Apr. (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2019 May. (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Education Committee, 2019 May 9. (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Full Board, 2019 May 20-23. (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Massage Therapy Advisory Board, 2019 May 29. (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2019 June. (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Telephone Conference Call, 2019 June 27. (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2019 July. (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Education Committee, 2019 July 10. (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Full Board, 2019 July 16-17. (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2019 Aug. (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Public Hearing - Elimination of Prescriptive Authority, 2019 Aug 27. (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Special Conference Committees, 2019 Aug. (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Telephone Conference Call, 2019 Aug 6. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2019 Sept. (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Education Committee, 2019 Sept 10. (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Full Board, 2019 Sept 16-20. (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2019 Oct. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Committee of the Joint Boards of Nursing and Medicine, 2019 Oct 16. (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Public Hearing - Autonomous Practice proposed legisltion, 2019 Oct 16. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Special Conference Committees, 2019 Oct. (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Telephone Conference Call, 2019 Oct. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2019 Nov. (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Education Committee, 2019 Nov 6. (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Full Board, 2019 Nov 19-21. (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2019 Dec. (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Committee of the Joint Boards of Nursing and Medicine, 2019 Dec 4. (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Special Conference Committees, 2019 Dec. (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Telephone Conference Calls, 2019 Dec. (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2020 Jan. (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Education Committee, 2020 Jan 15. (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Full Board, 2020 Jan 27-30. (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2020 Feb. (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Committee of the Joint Boards of Nursing and Medicine, 2020 Feb 12. (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Special Conference Committees, 2020 Feb. (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2020 Mar. (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Telephone Conference Call, 2020 Mar 18. (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Telephone Conference Call, 2020 Apr 21. (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Telephone Conference Call, 2020 May 7. (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Telephone Conference Calls, 2020 June. (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Committee of the Joint Boards of Nursing and Medicine, 2020 July 21. (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Education Committee, 2020 July 8. (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Full Board, 2020 July 21-22. (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2020 Aug. (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Committee of the Joint Boards of Nursing and Medicine, 2020 Aug 18. (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Special Conference Committees, 2020 Aug. (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Telephone Conference Call, 2020 Aug 13. (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2020 Sept. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Education Committee, 2020 Sept. (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - full Board, 2020 Sept 14-17. (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Telephone Conference Call, 2020 Sept 2. (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Web-Ex Training, 2020 Sept 29. (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2020 Oct. (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Committee of the Joint Boards of Nursing and Medicine, 2020 Oct 21. (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Full Board, 2020 Oct 14. (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Special Conference Committees, 2020 Oct. (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Telephone Conference Call, 2020 oct 27. (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, 2020 Nov. (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Full Board, 2020 Nov 16-19. (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Massage Therapy Advisory Board, 2020 Nov 2. (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Agency Subordinate Informal Conference, 2020 Dec 14. (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Committee for the Joint Boards of Nursing and Medicine, 2020 Dec 9. (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Full Board, 2020 Dec 2. (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Special Conference Committees, 2020 Dec. (Box 11, Folder 17)